The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Qiu Siping said
that this cave belonged to an ancient cultivator.
Maybe one of these texts has hints about the Ji Realm.
Found it !
There is only a single way to overcome
the limits of the Ji Realm:
Abandon the cultivation the Ji Realm granted you.
Shatter your cultivation.
After shattering your cultivation,
the Ji Realm will dissipate.
This is the only way to escape the Ji Realm.
Cultivate from zero
and redo all your breakthroughs.
Does that mean that you need to discard your Ancient God body ?
Not necessarily.
The Divine Path... So this is the Divine Path !
Create an avatar to cultivate simultaneously with the main body
and merge the two bodies to form a Nascent Soul.
I can use the Divine Path to create an avatar and form my Nascent Soul.
How is that any different ?
Master, the avatar must also cultivate from scratch
to the Nascent Soul breakthrough
and merge with the original body to attempt to form a Nascent Soul.
I wasn't able to form an avatar before
because I didn't have enough pills and artifacts.
With the harvest from the Land of the Ancient God,
this looks like the perfect time and place to try.
It's too risky !
The avatar's lifespan will only be 30 years !
If you don't form a Nascent Soul within 30 years,
it will all be for nothing !
Besides...
No need to discuss this any further,
I must form Nascent Soul in order to get revenge.
The country of Chu is at the north of the Burning Fire country
and at the east of the country of Xuanwu.
It also shares a border with the Sea of Devils
next to the Broken Rocks Mountains.
Its territory is vast
and is populated by many cultivators.
Even if it's just a rank 3 country,
it's at the pinnacle of rank 3 countries thanks to the Cloud Sky Sect,
Cloud Sky Sect
Country of Chu
a major sect specialized in alchemy.
It will eventually produce a Soul Formation cultivator and rise to rank 4.
Cheng Fei
Sword Qi Sect disciple
Late stage Foundation Establishment
Cheng Ling
Early stage Foundation Establishment
We are still 1000 li away,
why did we land here ?
If I want to become a disciple
then why do I have to walk ?
Keep your voice down,
everyone else is walking too.
This is a show of respect towards the sect.
Big Brother, why do you want me to join the Cloud Sky Sect ?
I don’t want to refine pills,
I want to join Sword Qi Sect like you !
Don't say that.
You know that
the Cloud Sky Sect is the strongest in the country of Chu.
The Cloud Sky Sect once refined a grade 5 pill.
In order to buy that pill, a rank 4 country
specially created a formation for the Cloud Sky Sect
that even ordinary rank 4 countries would struggle to break.
What do you think now ?
Well, that does pique my interest a bit.
Very well,
once I join the Cloud Sky Sect,
I will make pills
to help you in your cultivation.
You...
Do you think entering Cloud Sky Sect will be easy ?
They only recruit every 30 years.
Not only do major families of Chu send their descendents here
but many rogue cultivators also try their chance.
Thousands will participate
but less than 10 will be accepted.
Don’t worry,
a girl as adorable as me
is sure to be chosen.
You might not know
but the Cloud Sky Sect's recruitment is quite peculiar.
Unlike other sects that value talent and spiritual roots,
they value fate.
Big Brother, look at that person !
Why are his clothes are so funny ?
Hey, are you here to join the sect as well ?
Why are you dressed like a beggar ?
Hey, are you mute ?
I’m talking to you.
It's a pointless question.
Why else would I be heading to the Cloud Sky Sect ?
Wang Lin's avatar
3rd layer of Qi Condensation
You...
You’ve always been spoiled for being cute
but you rarely get ignored.
Let’s go.
It’s been so long since I felt the fatigue of a mortal.
Master,
why must you participate in this disciple selection ?
I came out of the Sea of Devils
specifically for this place.
If I can become a sect disciple,
I will use the Cloud Sky Sect's help
to form my Nascent Soul.
The will of the heavens is unpredictable...
I never thought that I'd join a sect again one day.
Incredible !
Among the candidates
there are 2nd and 3rd layers of Qi Condensation
and also people up to Core Formation.
Zhou Lin
Cloud Sky Sect 9th generation disciple
Early stage Core Formation
If you wish to join the Cloud Sky Sect,
your seniority will be low.
If you’re not willing, then leave now.
Since no one left,
then let's start.
The Cloud Sky Sect’s disciple selection begins now !
It’s starting, it’s starting !
Using whatever method you choose,
as long as you can feel what substance is inside this pillar
then you'll be qualified.
You have 6 hours.
I saw nothing !
Watch me !
My artifact !
He lost his artifact ?
You may use any method you can think of.
Don’t worry,
your artifacts will be returned after the selection.
My turn !
I’ll try too !
Me too !
I don't believe it !
Master, why aren’t you moving yet ?
There clearly is some kind of restriction to prevent anyone from probing.
What a coincidence,
you’re an Enlightened of Ancient God restrictions.
Even if this avatar doesn't have your cultivation,
you still have all the memories of the Ancient God.
Master is truly impressive.
Even without his cultivation or Ji Realm,
he still has a domineering aura around him.
11 Eleven pills,
11 jade slips
and 11 tokens engraved with pill furnaces.
Why are there different items ?
Wait...
the Cloud Sky Sect isn't selecting experts in restrictions.
Someone found it ?
Look over there !
How did she do it ?
She's no ordinary girl.
So you can actually take these things out ?
You pass.
So the real selection has nothing to do with the candidate.
It's the items inside that choose the disciples.
The 3 kinds of items
correspond to 3 different outcomes.
What are the outcomes ?
We won't know until we try.
I... I passed !
It's a pity this pill is of the fire element.
Otherwise, I could've been your teacher.
Congratulations on becoming an inner disciple of the Cloud Sky Sect.
Keep this pill.
The jade slip means you pass this trial
You will give it to your teacher
and the pill makes you an inner disciple directly.
to thank him for accepting you as disciple.
Then what is the token ?
Only 1 hour is left before the end of the test.
I can tell you
that there are 4 types of items in this pillar.
Jade slips, pills, tokens, and a pill furnace.
A pill furnace ?
Those who obtain jade slips
pass this test.
Those who obtain a pill
directly become inner sect disciples
Those who obtain a token
also become inner disciples
and can exchange the token for a grade 3 pill.
If you can obtain the pill furnace,
you will become a core disciple directly under the Sect Leader.
Master, quickly find it !
Everyone will admire you !
You'll have countless pills !
I won't waste time.
Being an inner disciple is enough.
Water element !?
Will you be my disciple ?
Then I’ll accept this gift.
I got one too !
I also have one !
You got one ?
Look at mine !
The Dragonborn Furnace !
A Sect Leader disciple will appear !--
Who is this lucky ?
Look up there !
What happened ?
Still, he failed.
Over the past 8000 years of the Cloud Sky Sect
only 6 Seniors ever got the pill furnace.
Sometimes, you need a little luck in life.
But you can't rely on luck alone.
This concludes this test of the disciple selection.
Those who failed will be escorted out.
Those who obtained items,
follow me up the mountain.
Understood !
Such a domineering pill furnace...
The buildings are entirely made of jade.
This alchemy sect must be really wealthy !
Such abundant spiritual energy !
The Cloud Sky Sect really is an excellent place for cultivation.
Song Qing
Cloud Sky Sect Leader
Middle stage Nascent Soul
9th generation disciple Zhou Lin, pays respects to Sect Leader.
Here are the 6 who passed the disciple selection.
3 obtained jade slips
2 obtained pills
and 1 obtained a token.
Those who obtained jade slips
will have to undergo a second test
to decide whether they become inner disciples.
Understood.
Those who obtained pills
will take 9th generation disciples as their teacher.
Junior Sun, you choose your disciple first.
Thank you, Sect Leader.
Sun Zhenwei
9th generation Cloud Sky Sect disciple
Late stage Core Formation
Sect Leader, disciple wishes to take this person as disciple.
He obtained a water element pill
that perfectly matches my current needs for alchemy.
Junior Sun, are you willing to yield this person ?
Zhou Lin is Elder Li’s only disciple.
Naturally, I wish to help him.
Thank you.
Then who will you choose ?
Disciple pays respects to Teacher.
You haven’t obtained inner disciple qualifications yet.
You can't choose your teacher yet.
This girl is quite clever.
Although you only obtained a jade slip,
your courage is commendable.
I’ll make an exception and take you as my disciple.
As for the inner disciple,
I'll take him.
Sect Leader,
is this acceptable ?
This... this is against the sect's rules.
No problem, no problem.
Since Junior Sun has spoken,
then let it be so.
But...
You're dismissed.
Understood.
The Cloud Sky Sect is divided into the inner and outer sect.
The inner sect refines pills
and the outer sect guards it.
Since you are an inner disciple,
you will focus on alchemy.
Such extravagance !
There are so many precious plants
in this disciple's garden !
Wang Lin,
you are my first disciple.
From now on,
you will live in this room.
I will go in seclusion for several months
to absorb the Water Spirit Pill.
You will find
my insights on alchemy inside this jade slip
along with pill formulas.
Read them for yourself.
I will teach you personally when I come out.
You may freely use
the herbs in this garden.
But remember, don’t uproot them.
And this furnace
is my greeting gift for you.
Thank you, Teacher !
During my seclusion,
if you have any questions about alchemy,
go find your Grandteacher.
She is very kind
and will explain to you the details
about the inner workings of alchemy.
Alright,
I should go now.
Just a heads up,
you’re still young
so while I’m in seclusion,
take good care of yourself
and remember to never cut corners.
This small pill furnace
is the same quality as the Hundred Beasts Spirit Furnace I traded for in the Sea of Devils.
This cheap Master of yours
is surprisingly kind.
Teacher, Teacher !
I have a disciple !
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.